Hey, anyone there?
Anyone there? Hey!
Shut up!
Ah!
Who's that? There's no air.
Who are you? Why am I here? Hey!
It's no use.
And you are?
I've been knocking
while you were sleeping.
We're stuck in here.
Was I k… kidnapped?
And why are we at sea?
It's no use.
Jung found out.
That's it.
Jung? You… you mean my boss?
W… what does he know?
You work for Jung too, huh?
I'm his accountant.
How could you do it?
-What?
-I'm only his driver.
How could I turn it down?
Uh, turn… turn down what?
Can you please explain?
How can you be the accountant
at a huge construction company
and still get around
to sleep with his wife?
Sleep with his wife?
How could I sleep with her?
Then why are you here?
Uh, Jung can't possibly think…
I've only met her twice.
Don't make excuses.
You're locked in here just like me.
Huh…
I guess they'll just toss us
into the ocean.
I guess he wants to silence me.
He already believes
that I leaked information about fraud.
Is that so?
Jung launders money
for a lot of political and financial VIPs.
Everyone knows that.
Someone set me up.
If I wanted to rat him out,
I would have already done it.
If you left proof
with someone close to you…
…then after we're dead,
they could expose the asshole.
We could have our revenge.
My wife might see the ledgers in my study.
But she's not the sort of person
who would…
She wouldn't dare do anything.
My son just started junior high.
I… I don't… I, uh…
They're in the study?
Huh?
Next time, you're doing the dirty work.
-We appreciate all your help.
-Wait, I…
And you'll have a guy round
to copy those ledgers sometime.
I'm that guy.
Don't worry.
We're not going to hurt your family.
There's food and drinks over there.
Help yourself.
Wait, wait!
But if you're thinking of stopping us,
work out how you'll explain this to Jung.
My wife might see the ledgers in my study.
But she's not the sort of person
who would…
We're on our way to get the ledgers.
If there's no shocks, nobody's shocked.
After you get them, hurry back.
The chairman's got a new task.
Hey. Do we have to keep doing jobs
for the cops?
I'm starting to feel like one of them.
If the case comes from the director
of the National Police Agency,
how can we turn it down?
If you've got complaints,
tell them to the chairman.
THE FIXERS
THE SWAMP EEL
Come on, gentlemen.
If you don't gamble your money,
your parents get funny.
Chance is untaken and bets are forsaken.
A bet or two, money for you.
-Okay.
-Come on.
-Come on!
-Bets are placed. No more changes.
All right!
Open!
Triples triumph again.
Triples beat all. Come to Papa.
-Come on.
-You should never gamble.
-What? Keep going.
-You can't leave. You've just won.
Sorry, gents.
My beautiful wife's made me dinner.
-Who do you think you're kidding?
-Your wife's waiting with your dinner.
I don't have a wife now. Keep going.
We're not done.
Just wait there.
Come on!
Hanshan temples outside Gusu.
The rightful path
will sometimes choose you.
Hurry up.
Hey, Milky.
-What's this, huh?
-Pond Loach.
Well, well, well…
Business seems all right.
How are you? I'm Swamp Eel.
-Yeah.
-Huh? Coffee, tea, or me?
I'll make it for you.
Oh, will you just…
Your debt's overdue. Time to pay.
Well, uh, uh,
business is not so great lately, so…
What about we have another game here?
Come on! Let's go again!
Huh? Huh?
Let's do it.
We good? Okay.
Oh!
Look at that.
-Are you sure?
-All in on big.
Here we go, here we go!
-Big.
-Bet on big.
-Okay.
-Bet on big!
Okay, all right.
Bets are placed. No more changes.
Like a lamb to the slaughter.
Here we go.
Go big or go home.
Open it. Open it. Big!
What's up? Scared, are you?
What?
You're scared?
Open!
Hey! Fuck you! You're fixing this!
-Whoa! No.
-What the hell was that?
No, no, let's talk it over.
The fan was on too high,
so it blew the dice over.
-I'm not cheating here.
-Keep talking shit. That's fine.
You think I don't know
what your most valuable body part is,
your golden index finger, huh?
I heard your last boss even put
an insurance policy on it.
You hear what I'm saying?
Mm-hmm?
Okay. I'll just pay the amount.
All right?
Hey, move. Out of the way. Move.
-Hey, come on, come on. What's going on?
-Take the money, take the money. Come on.
Pay, my ass!
Get him!
-Granny, I gotta go.
-Debt collectors?
-No!
-Ah, what an asshole.
Ah!
Stop there!
Hey!
-Uh, I'll leave you to it. Shit!
-Stop!
-Ahh!
-Come on, come on!
We gotta go, man!
We lost him.
Where is he? Fuck!
There he is. Stop running, man!
Stop! Stop!
What's he doing?
Asshole!
-He's climbing the wall!
-Fucking monkey!
Shit. Hey! Hey!
Fuck!
Ridiculous.
He's in here. Stop!
Shh, shh! Shh, shh, shh, shh!
-Hello?
-Dad, I think we're screwed.
-What are you telling me for?
-I'm not talking about you.
It's Mom who's in trouble.
He's over there! He's over there!
-Fucking traitor!
-Stop!
Stop running. Fuck!
Fucking stop!
Stop, you old motherfucking gorilla!
Fuck this shit!
Stop! Stop!
-Hey, what's with all this?
-I catch you, you're fucking dead!
Here we are!
-Hey, my swamp eel!
-Eurgh!
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Motherfucker!
Fuck you, motherfucker!
Piece of shit!
Fuck you! Where are you going?
Come back, fucker!
Just stop, motherfucker!
Stop this fighting!
Get out of my store!
What are you doing?
Please don't touch that!
He's there!
I'm gonna call the police!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Stop this!
-Get out!
-Fucking stop him!
Get out of my store!
Call us if you have any issues. Bye.
Hey! Hey, officer, here.
-You okay, sir?
-Can you give me a ride home?
What's wrong?
Well, you know, I have diabetes.
And the insulin, you know, the syringe,
I didn't bring it with me.
Do you need an ambulance?
No, it's quicker if you give me a ride.
-Okay, watch your head.
-Thank you, thank you.
Get his address.
We'll drop him off on the way.
See ya!
Mwah!
Wu Song fights the tiger.
SCAMMERS, FACE US AND PAY UP
Hey, buddy, what happened?
Where's your mom?
-Live streaming.
-And exactly why is she live streaming?
Take a look.
He then told me to buy
some kind of cryptocurrency, so I did…
WENDY'S SEAFOOD LIVE STREAMING
…and it multiplied a hundredfold.
Can you believe it?
Then he said
this company would release a new coin.
He said that the price
would definitely go up
and told me I had to buy it,
so I bought it. Look.
-Half a month later, 12%.
-Not again.
My husband always says
take advantage when you're up,
and when you're down, go all out!
-So of course…
-You hear that from me?
-Well, yeah.
-Did I say that?
Hey, they're your words.
You should remember.
The price goes up. I wanna cash out.
What does the company tell me?
They're under investigation.
They won't give me any of it back.
That's all right though. It's only 5 mil.
I promise it'll be shipped out next month,
fresh and delivered direct to you.
When has Wendy Wu ever lied to you?
-Uh…
-So this investment is a scam already?
-Report it to the cops.
-I went to the police, didn't I?
And there's a possibility
that I can't get it back.
Just wait.
I'm the casualty here,
so you should be nice to me and not shout.
All day you play mahjong, which is okay,
but you've been scammed
out of 5 million. That's not.
I'm the one who should be yelling.
You go out all day,
and you come back,
your clothes are all dirty.
-I'm starting to think you've got a lover.
-Hey!
You're obsessed with getting rich.
Scammers love people like that.
Felix Chiang.
You have no right to go on with that talk.
I've been married to you for so long.
This is how I'm treated?
I have to raise a child
on next to nothing.
I worked to help out with expenses.
We'd be living on the street
if we relied on you.
So this is all on me, is it?
It's my fault now.
I'm not saying that.
I… I just, uh…
I just wanna earn a little extra money.
Money can be earned back.
-At the very worst, I'll take care of it.
-Hey.
That was a lot of money.
You can't cover that.
Please, don't you know who I am?
Back in the day, this kind of money
was nothing to me, okay?
Hey. Where'd you get 5 million?
Oh. Uh… uh…
Uh, I just…
I just used our house as collateral
and took out a loan in your name.
Astounding!
Great investing!
CHIU CHA TEMPLE
Excuse me, miss. Are you seeking guidance?
CONSULTATION FORM, CHAO MING-CHENG
Please draw a fortune stick.
That's all you need.
FANG CHIAO-HUI
The fortune slip reads,
"The one who ties the knot
must be the one to untie it."
If Mr. Chao encounters any difficulties,
tell him to come handle it himself.
How did it go?
CHING HE TEMPLE
They want you to go there in person.
-This way, please, sir.
-Thank you.
CHAO MING-CHENG
Mr. Chao.
Do you have a problem?
Please come with me.
TAI SUI HALL
I am the chairman of Ching He,
Thackery Huang.
Tell me why you're here.
How can I assist you, sir?
As his term draws to an end,
Attorney Chao Ming-cheng
is seeking re-election,
but news has broken
of his son's drug possession.
A leaked video clearly shows
an unidentified…
What do you think of this?
The party hacks will switch
their allegiance to Lu Shu-jung
and force Chao Ming-cheng to withdraw.
Then congratulations.
Lu Shu-jung is a conservative
within the party.
If she's elected, that'll help
your chances of becoming mayor.
-The minister's here.
-It's the minister.
MING YOUNG PARTY FUNDRAISER
TRISTAN HSUEH AND FATHER ARRIVE AT EVENT
Word is you're active post retirement.
If your son becomes mayor,
would you be pulling the strings?
-Sir, please comment.
-Uh, tonight's a fundraising dinner.
-Let's focus on that.
-Sir, can you stop for a photo?
Louis.
Join us.
-Come on.
-What? Who is he?
-Is this the other son?
-No, no, no, that's impossible.
There's only one son.
I've never seen him before.
Stand in the middle.
Yung? Hi. Why are you calling?
Just to warn you
that Milky's spreading the word
that you rig your games.
And I heard your family was scammed,
and you owe 5 million.
How'd you know that?
Because your wife live-streamed
her sob story to the whole world.
Everyone knows. What's your plan?
Uh, I'll change location, I guess.
I'll find someplace.
I'll pay off the debts before I die
and make a little more
for my wife and son.
I got a job that could turn a quick buck.
Someone owes my friend money.
You've just got to flash a gun around
as a warning.
I won't work with guns. Got that?
You used to be such a badass.
If you come back--
Evening light upon my heart.
You'll soon be dead, so fart.
That was a long time ago, okay?
Hey, you're perfect for this
'cause I know you won't pull the trigger.
For 300,000, you don't have to shoot.
You just flash it around. Well?
I thought you heard me.
I don't pull a gun these days.
Think it over. I'll call you again later.
Tsk. Keep looking.
Dad. What are you looking for?
Uh, don't scare me like that.
Have you come across a…
a… tin box with flowers on it?
No. Why do you want that?
-Hey, you need to know.
-What?
You'll need to earn big
to support your mom. Don't be like me.
Hey, you shouldn't
underestimate her, okay?
She's live streaming so much,
she'll earn it back.
How's she feeling?
She's on the phone to aunt saying,
"How could I be so stupid
as to sell the house?"
Anyway, you've heard it all before.
Ah.
Found it.
-What's in there?
-Nothing. Why?
You got midterms tomorrow. Go learn, huh?
Hey, buddy.
What?
Good luck, yeah.
Ooh, what's in the bag, buddy?
Hey!
-Hello?
-Hi.
Have you made up your mind?
Stop thinking about it. It's decided.
I'll send you the address.
Shit.
Mr. Hung, it's been a while.
Yes, long time no see.
This is my son Tristan.
-Oh.
-And this is Mr. Wang.
Please meet Mr. Chen.
Sir, hello. Pleased to meet you.
Please look after this young man.
Young and very promising.
Hey, hello. It's been a long time, sir.
Should I be addressing you
as Legislator Lu?
Oh, no. But seriously,
the position might be decided
a little earlier tonight.
When you take office as a legislator,
I'm sure you'll have lots of plans.
It'll be fine.
I'll oversee the Hsin Nan
Redevelopment Zone project personally.
There won't be any hitches.
Give me a vodka martini.
Shaken, not stirred.
Make it a double.
I don't need to be sober for this.
What are you having?
Oh, orange juice.
Oh. You don't need alcohol for this?
I'm working. I can't drink.
One more, thanks.
Work's an excellent excuse to drink.
Louis Hsueh. Hello.
The son of ex-Minister Hsueh?
Well, hello. I'm Lu Shu-jung's aide, Viki.
I don't think I've seen you
around here before.
My dad doesn't usually bring me
to these things.
I'm not very social.
So I see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
-Your trousers.
-It's fine.
You owe me now.
We could exchange numbers.
Sorry. I didn't expect
you to be so forward.
There were so many people downstairs.
You've done this a lot.
What does that mean?
I can't believe a graduate with a PhD
had to hook up with her boss's husband
just to get the gig of a PA.
Why do you have that picture?
I ask the questions.
What do you want from me?
Chao Ming-cheng's son's drug use is a fix.
Who did you hire to do it?
Uh, I don't know what you're asking me.
Should I give these
to the press at the event?
Or should I post them online?
You're trying to send me mad.
I don't have to.
You can just tell me
who you hired to frame him.
Hmm.
Lu Shu-jung's husband did it.
He hired Noods.
In exchange for what?
Once Lu Shu-jung is elected,
Noods's charges will be thrown out.
Is Lu Shu-jung that clever?
She definitely isn't.
Once she's elected,
I'll get someone to report Noods
and accuse him of kidnap and trafficking.
If she denies everything, she'll be fine.
Once she's elected,
I'll get someone to report Noods
and accuse him of kidnap and trafficking.
If you don't tell anyone
what we discussed here,
then you and these shots are in the clear.
As his term draws to an end,
Attorney Chao Ming-cheng
is seeking re-election,
but news has broken
of his son's drug possession.
A leaked video clearly shows
an unidentified powdery substance
surrounding his son's body.
-Hey.
-You about to go in?
How come it's a pig farm?
Um, it's a cover
for Noods's drug distribution company.
Something doesn't feel right.
What? Oh, you've been out of the game
for too long.
You lost your nerve.
Don't worry. No one knows you're coming.
All right.
Noods.
Is risking your life like this
for them worth it?
Hey. How much are you earning?
I don't know what you're talking about,
so go on, shoot me.
And I don't earn anything.
Stubborn, aren't you?
She definitely isn't. When she's elected,
I'll get someone to report Noods
and accuse him of kidnap and trafficking.
If she denies everything, she'll be fine.
After they're done using you,
they're gonna make you wear it.
Fuck that. You can't trust a politician.
What do you want?
As long as you give me the proof
that Mr. Chao's son was framed,
I promise
you'll get out of this all right, okay?
You'll even earn something.
It's in the pigsty there.
Buddy.
I didn't mean to shoot you.
I didn't see anything.
You don't work for Noods?
No. I was sent here to collect a debt.
Uh…
There is a bag there. Bring it here.
GOLD
-Hello?
-So, have you got it yet?
I've been shot.
Where are you? I've got you.
Don't worry.
It's too late.
I'll send the file to you now. Hold on.
Oh motherfucking shit.
I got the video, but the phone's broken,
so I can't send it.
There's someone there.
-Hello?
-Our client goes on stage in half an hour.
Have you found the evidence yet?
Help me find someone first.
I'll send you a photo.
FELIX CHIANG, SWAMP EEL
55 YEARS OLD
Put me on speaker.
Felix Chiang.
Who's that?
Bring that phone to the top floor
of the Kuang He Road parking lot
within 20 minutes.
Hand it over to a red sports car.
Here's a question. Why should I?
Howie Chiang. Your son's got a great name.
He goes to Ping Cheng Junior High
and ranks high in his class.
How do you know that? Tell me.
Twenty minutes.
You have only 20 minutes
to bring the phone here,
and I guarantee
your family will be safe and sound.
If you don't come, you're on your own.
-Asshole.
-Thank you.
Oh fuck!
Hey, is that your car?
Come on, hurry up.
Mr. Chao.
Ten minutes until you go on stage.
All prepared?
Don't be so arrogant.
I'll settle this score with you
sooner or later.
Fine. I'll be ready for you.
Sir, get ready to go on stage.
The host will go over
the order of events with you.
They should be free in a minute.
-We can't get hold of Noods.
-What happened?
The tracker shows…
I don't care what you do. Sort it out.
BREAD AND CAKES
Hurry up.
-Here.
-Oof!
Eau de swine?
-Funny guy, huh?
-Stand over there, will you?
Hey, wait. You got what you want,
so I'm done.
You wait. I need to check it.
Shit.
Hey, hurry up.
Give this phone to Mr. Chao Ming-cheng
at the fundraising dinner next door.
You should do it. I don't give a shit.
This is nonsense.
I hear your son's in the top 30 at school.
It'd be a pity to lose him over this.
That's him. Get him.
Uh…
Stop! Stop!
Bastard! Stop!
-Where's he going?
-Go, go, go! Fuck!
Catch him!
-Come back!
-Stop!
-Stop running. Fuck you.
-Stop chasing, I'll stop running.
MING YOUNG PARTY
Good, evening everyone.
I am Chao Ming-cheng.
Thank you for all your support
along the way.
I have worked hard
ever since I entered politics
to serve the people.
And I have never done anything
against my conscience.
However, over the years,
my views have changed.
All right, that's enough.
Where's the stuff
you're going to give Chao Ming-cheng?
Speak up.
You're not listening to me.
That's all on the phone, man.
I'm not stupid. It's just porn movies.
Does he like watching porn a lot?
I don't care.
I've had enough of your shit.
Now beat him to death.
CHING HE TEMPLE
Marathon man.
Fuck you.
Fucking rabbit.
Chickenshit.
Over time…
…I have devoted my life to work…
and neglected my family.
So, after careful consideration,
I formally announce…
I have to tell you…
…that I will not be withdrawing.
I have evidence that proves
that allegations of my son's drug use
are entirely fabricated.
I will fight this by-election.
I will continue to serve.
And I will never stand down.
This doesn't look right.
Sprinkle a bit more powder. On him too.
MISSION COMPLETE
Get out!
You enjoy that, asshole, huh?
How'd you get out of that?
Fuck! It takes a lot more than that
to bring me down.
-They were nothing to me.
-Get in. We'll share a late dinner.
Fuck you!
Don't let me see you again!
Fixer Shadow has been sent for treatment.
The surveillance shots near the scene,
they're destroyed.
Then we can ask Mr. Chao
to make a donation.
Very well.
There is another matter
that you might be interested in.
CELESTIAL
EARTH
ARCANE
TERRA
PRIMORDIUM
The cryptocurrency market
is of course celebrating
this incredible surge.
The CEO of well-known domestic
cryptocurrency platform Yuan Tao
made a surprising statement
during an interview.
He believes that the current surge
is just the beginning.
Significant movements in…
Where the hell have you been?
You weren't answering your phone.
Uh, I had stuff to do
with the gaming house.
Why the hell are you sleeping here?
I was waiting for you.
Hey, what happened?
Your face is covered in scratches.
Uh, some asshole flashed their high beams,
and I fell over.
Go get some rest.
-Will you be careful?
-Yeah, yeah.
Chao Ming-cheng said
that he would not bow to malicious forces
no matter how much pressure he faced.
CHAO MING-CHENG SHARES VIDEO
CLAIMING SON WAS FRAMED IN DRUG CASE
He will fight for justice.
In other news, at a nearby hospital,
multiple mobsters have been injured
and taken to hospital
with kneecap fractures.
Attorney Chao Ming-cheng
stressed that he would never bow
to malicious forces.
No matter how much pressure he faces,
he will persist in speaking out
for the people and for the truth.
After the press conference concluded,
a shooting occurred at a nearby hospital.
Known criminal gangs were implicated…
Oh, you frightened me there.
Are you having a nightmare?
What exactly were you busy with
last night?
The largest local gang…
You came home covered in scratches
and kept checking the news.
…large event with 100 gang members
dressed in black.
To prevent any accidents,
the police deployed over 100 officers.
Yeah.
So was Noods scared shitless to see you?
I just need to say, I didn't kill Noods.
It was someone else who did it.
What? What, Noods is dead?!
-You haven't heard he's dead?
-Damn it!
-I thought you never pulled the trigger.
-What?
I, I, I didn't ask you to kill him.
-Don't call me again. I can't believe it.
-What part are you not hearing?
Shit!
A fundraising dinner last night
was attended by the Hsueh family,
including prospective mayor Tristan Hsueh.
Today, he made a major move
by presenting a municipal study
targeting traffic congestion.
TAI SUI HALL